hi folks this is Matt Jackson again and
嗨，大家好，我是Matt Matt Jackson
so now let's take a look at mixed
现在让我们来看看混合
strategy Nash equilibrium in practice
实践中的策略纳什均衡
yeah I've been trying to understand a
是的，我一直在努力理解
little bit about what it can tell us
关于它可以告诉我们的一点点
about what we should expect to see so
关于我们应该期望看到的
let's start with a situation of soccer
让我们从足球的情况开始
penalty kicks
罚点球
and this is a quite natural application
这是一个很自然的应用
of mixed strategy equilibria because
混合策略均衡的原因是
they're ubiquitous in sports and
他们在运动中无处不在
competitive games so situations where it
竞技游戏，在这种情况下
actually pays to be unpredictable so by
实际上付出了不可预测的代价
not knowing what the other the
不知道其他的
opposition is going to do it makes it a
反对派将这样做
little more difficult for you to pick an
让您难以选择
optimal strategy in these games where
这些游戏中的最佳策略
one player wins and the other player
一个玩家获胜，另一个玩家
loses and in particular in soccer
输，尤其是足球
penalty kicks we're looking at a
点球大战，我们正在寻找
situation where a kicker has to try and
踢手不得不尝试的情况
kick the ball into the goal the goalie
将球踢入守门员
can try and move to deflect the ball and
可以尝试移动以使球偏向
this happens very quickly so it's
这发生得很快，所以
essentially a simultaneous move game the
本质上是同时移动游戏
kicker is choosing to go either in their
踢球者选择要么进入他们
simplified version say to the right or
简化版本说在右边或
the left the goalie is then gonna dive
左边的守门员将要潜水
to the to one side or the other side and
到一侧或另一侧，
try to deflect the ball and if the
尝试使球偏转，如果
goalie guesses correctly it ends up in
守门员正确猜出它最终以
the same direction as the kicker then
然后与踢脚方向相同
they have a high chance of higher chance
他们有较高的机会
of saving it if they go in an opposite
如果他们走了相反的话，保存它
direction they have a lower chance of
方向，他们有较低的机会
saving it okay so how are equilibrium
可以节省下来，那么平衡如何
stencil that I might be biased I might
模具，我可能有偏见，我可能
be able to kick the ball more accurately
能够更准确地踢球
in one direction than the other so if
在一个方向比另一个方向
you ask me to kick it towards the left
你问我把它踢向左边
side of the goal it might be that I hit
目标的一面可能是我击中了
there very accurately if you tell me I
如果你告诉我我就很准确
have to kick it towards the right side
必须将其踢向右侧
of the goal it could be that I'm less
目标可能是我少了
accurate and I have a higher chance of
准确，我有更高的机会
just missing the goal all together so
只是一起错过了目标
how is the equilibrium going to adjust
平衡如何调整
when we change one of the players
当我们更换一名球员时
adjustments and in terms of their skills
调整以及他们的技能
so let's have a peek at this
让我们来看看
so the kicker who kicks penalty kicks
所以踢罚球的踢脚踢
worse to the right than the left kick
右脚比左脚还差
more often to the left than the right so
左边比右边多
if I if I'm worse and kicking towards
如果我如果我更糟，踢向
the right does that mean I should kick
正确的意思是我应该踢
in the opposite direction more often
相反的方向
well let's have a peek so let's start
好吧，让我们来看看，让我们开始吧
with just the simple version
只是简单的版本
to get our ideas fixed so imagine that
修正我们的想法，想象一下
the setting is one where the kicker and
该设置是其中踢脚和
a goalie if they so let's have the
守门员，如果他们愿意，让我们
kicker on this side so the kicker is the
这边的踢腿，所以踢腿是
row player the goalie is the column
行球员守门员是列
player and if they end up kicking
球员，如果他们最终踢
if the kicker goes left and the goalie
如果踢脚向左走，守门员
also happens to go to the left then the
也碰巧到左边然后
goalie saves and the goalie gets a
守门员保存，守门员得到
payoff of 1 the kicker gets a payoff of
收益为1，踢球者的收益为
0 if instead we're in a situation where
如果相反，我们处于一种情况
say the kicker goes left and the goalie
说踢手走了，守门员
goes right then the kicker scores and
正确，然后踢球得分，
gets a payoff of 1 and and so forth ok
得到1的收益，依此类推
so this is just a simple variation on
所以这只是一个简单的变化
matching pennies and in this situation
匹配的便士，在这种情况下
what's the equilibrium going to be the
什么是平衡
equilibrium is going to be quite simple
平衡将非常简单
it's just going to be that the kicker
只是踢球
randomizes equally between left and
在左和右之间平均随机分配
right the goalie randomizes between left
右边守门员在左边之间随机分组
and right each person has a probability
每个人都有机会
1/2 to win from kicking to the left to
从左踢到1/2获胜
right going left to right so it's a very
右从左到右，这是一个非常
simple game and we have a good idea of
简单的游戏，我们有一个好主意
how to solve that one ok so now what are
如何解决这个问题，那么现在是什么
we going to do let's change things and
我们要做的就是改变事物，
now we've got a kicker who sometimes
现在我们有一个踢人，有时
misses when they go to the right so in
当他们向右走时会错过
particular if the goalie happens to go
特别是守门员碰巧走
to the left and the goals wide open to
向左，目标向
the right the kicker
正确的踢脚
scores 75% of the time but actually
得分达到75％的时间，但实际上
misses completely 25% of the time okay
完全错过25％的时间
so this is a kicker who still does well
所以这是踢得很好的人
if they go left in the goalie goes to
如果他们在守门员左走
the opposite direction but now they have
相反的方向，但现在他们有了
a lower probability of winning when
较低的获胜概率
they're kicking right and they have a
他们踢的正确，他们有一个
wide-open goal ok so how should this
大开目标好，那该怎么办
adjust what's what should the new
调整新的内容
equilibrium look like so let's suppose
平衡看起来像这样，让我们​​假设
let's first of all try and keep the
让我们首先尝试保持
kicker indifferent so let's think of the
踢球者无动于衷，让我们想想
goalie going left with probability P
守门员以概率P向左走
right with probability 1 minus P for the
对的概率为1减去P
kicker to be indifferent what has to be
踢球者无动于衷
true well what's their payoff if they go
真的很好，如果他们去，他们的收益是什么
left
剩下
their payoff to going left is just 1
他们向左走的收益只有1
times 1 minus P their kickoff their
1乘以P，他们的开球
payoff to going right is 0.75 times P
向右的收益是P的0.75倍
these two things have to be equal in
这两个条件必须相等
order to have this the kicker be
为了让这个踢球
indifferent so what do we end up with we
漠不关心，所以我们最终会得到什么
end up with 0.75 P is equal to 1 minus P
最终0.75 P等于1减去P
so we end up with 1 equals 1.75 P or P
所以我们最终得到1等于1.75 P或P
is equal to 1 over 1.75 which is equal
等于1.75等于1
to 4 over 7 okay so that tells us that
到4比7好，这告诉我们
the goalie should be going left with
守门员应该和
probability 4/7 and right with
概率为4/7，右为
probability 3/7 okay so we know what the
概率为3/7，所以我们知道
goal is supposed to be doing so so now
目标应该现在就这样做
the fact that we changed the goalies
我们改变了守门员的事实
payoffs haven't changed but the fact
收益没有改变，但事实
that we changed the kicker's payoffs
我们改变了踢球者的收益
meant that the goalie actually had to
意味着守门员实际上不得不
adjust right so even though the goalies
调整正确，即使守门员
payoffs haven't changed at all in this
收益根本没有改变
game the new equilibrium has a different
游戏中新的平衡有不同
set of probabilities for the goalie in
守门员的一组概率
order to keep the kicker and different
为了保持踢脚和不同
now okay so now let's let's see what the
现在好了，现在让我们看看
kicker is going to do so how we see
踢手将这样做，我们如何看
what's so so let's suppose that the
怎么回事，让我们假设
kicker goes left with probability Q
踢手以概率Q向左走
right with probability 1 minus Q and
就以概率1减去Q和
must solve for Q well for the goalie to
必须为守门员很好地解决Q
be indifferent what is their payoff if
淡漠他们的收益是什么，如果
they go left if they're going left
他们要走就走
they're getting and they're getting a Q
他们正在得到Q
probability that they match so they get
他们匹配的概率，所以他们得到
Q plus 0.25 times 1 minus Q if they go
Q加0.25乘以1减去Q
left if they go right instead what are
如果他们向右走就向左走，那是什么
they getting they're just getting 1
他们得到他们只是得到1
minus Q right so these two things have
减去Q对，所以这两件事
to be equal so we end up with Q is equal
等于，所以我们得出Q等于
to 0.75 times 1 minus Q so Q over 1
到0.75乘以1减去Q，所以Q超过1
minus Q
负Q
is equal to 0.75 what does this tell us
等于0.75这告诉我们什么
about Q that tells us that Q is equal to
关于Q的告诉我们Q等于
3/7 okay so what's going to happen when
3/7好的，那么什么时候会发生
we work out this we get 3/7 for the
我们算出这个，我们得到3/7
probability that the kicker is going to
踢手将要去的概率
go left and 4/7 for the probability that
向左走和4/7的概率
the kicker is going to go right so
踢脚将要正确，所以
overall what do we have now we have the
总体而言，我们现在拥有的是
strategies looking like this as we made
我们制定的策略看起来像这样
this adjustment and we noticed two sort
这种调整，我们注意到两种
of interesting things about this one is
关于这个有趣的事情是
that the goalies payoffs didn't change
守门员的收益没有改变
but they still had to adjust their
但是他们仍然不得不调整他们的
strategies and the second is that the
策略，第二个是
kicker is actually kicking more often to
踢手实际上踢得更多
the weaker side right so the the right
较弱的一面，所以右边
foot got worse than it was before and
脚变得比以前更糟
they're actually going in that direction
他们实际上正在朝那个方向前进
more often and why is that it's because
更多，为什么是因为
the kicker the the goalie has also made
守门员还踢出的球
an adjustment in this game and so the
在这个游戏中的调整，所以
the comparative statics in mixed
混合中的比较静态
strategy Nash equilibria are actually
策略纳什均衡实际上是
quite subtle and somewhat
相当微妙和有点
counterintuitive in terms of what you
关于你的直觉
might expect you're you you get a bias
可能会期望你是你，你会有偏见
so that this becomes a weaker direction
所以这变成一个较弱的方向
and the equilibrium adjusts so that the
并调整平衡，以便
player goes in that direction more often
玩家更经常朝那个方向走
so let's have a look just through the
因此，让我们看一下
intuition here again in the goalie
守门员再次在这里直觉
strategy must have the kicker and
策略必须具有优势
different and so when we went through
不同，所以当我们经历
that those payoffs the the kicker the
那些回报使踢球者
goalie goes left more often than right
守门员向左走的次数多于向右走的次数
and the kicker actually so sorry there's
踢手实际上很抱歉
a typo here the kicker
错别字
actually goes right more frequently
实际上更正确
right goes right with probability now
正确的可能性现在正确
4/7 so they've increased their
4/7所以他们增加了他们的
probability on that and when we end up
最终发生的可能性
what we see is the the goalie strategy's
我们看到的是守门员策略
adjusting but we also see that the
调整，但我们也看到
kicker adjusts to kicking more to the
踢脚调整为向脚踢更多
towards their weak side so the the
朝向他们的弱点，所以
goalie now actually has a slighted
守门员现在实际上有点
so if you go through and calculate the
因此，如果您经过计算
probability that the goalie is going to
守门员要去的概率
win they're going to win 4/7 of the time
赢，他们将赢得4/7的时间
and this in this match and and we can
在这场比赛中，我们可以
think you know what would happen if the
以为你知道如果
goalie actually just stayed with their
守门员实际上只是和他们在一起
old strategy of still going 5050 then
仍然沿用5050的旧策略
the kicker could always go left and win
踢手总能向左走并赢
half the time instead of three sevens so
一半的时间而不是三七
the the fact that the goalie has to make
守门员必须做出的事实
an adjustment is because they have to
调整是因为他们必须
defend more to the left side to defer
防守更多，以推迟
because now the the kickers has a better
因为现在踢球者有更好的表现
chance of winning on that side so the
在那边获胜的机会，所以
goalie goes more in that direction that
守门员朝那个方向走得更多
pushes the the kicker towards their
将踢脚推向他们
weaker side in order to make sure that
较弱的一面，以确保
the goalie is willing to go in to the
守门员愿意进入
left side without her frequency so by
左边没有她的频率所以
adjusting the strategy to keep the
调整策略以保持
kicker indifferent the goalie actually
踢手实际上无视守门员
gets advantage of the kickers week right
正确利用踢球周
kick and and wins more often okay
踢和赢更多，好吗
so just in terms of summary and mixed
所以就总结和混合而言
strategies and soccer penalty kicks in
策略和足球处罚开始
general players must be indifferent
一般玩家必须漠不关心
between the things that they're
在他们之间的事物之间
randomizing over that produces very
随机产生非常
interesting and subtle comparative
有趣而微妙的比较
statics and you know there's a question
静力学，你知道有一个问题
it might come up in your mind you know
你可能会想到
do people really do this I mean this is
人们真的这样做吗？我的意思是
fairly complicated right so you know
相当复杂的权利，所以你知道
5050 we can figure out once we get these
5050我们一旦弄清这些就可以弄清楚
to these games where a player has an
这些玩家拥有
advantage one way or another then the
优势一种或另一种然后
actual mixture becomes fairly
实际的混合变得相当
complicated and it's not so obvious that
复杂，而且不是很明显
players will actually do that so we'll
玩家实际上会这样做，所以我们会
take a look at that and see if this
看看那个，看看是否
actually bears out in practice
实际上证明了